Yo, Jordan.
>> What's up?
>> You want to do city streets? Come on.
>> Yeah,
coming down.
>> [music]
[music]
>> So, every summer for the last 18 years,
the city of New York takes like a
handful of weekend days and calls them
Summer Streets. And what they do is they
they close down like the biggest avenues
in all five boroughs, and they're just
open to people on like bikes and
skateboards and stuff. It's like a It's
like a city-wide party. What are you
running?
>> Yeah, I like peak sun runs.
>> Get those miles.
>> Good to see you.
>> Summer Streets felt like a prime place
to try out the new X6.
>> Yo,
Casey.
What's up?
>> I've been working with Insta360 for like
3 or 4 years now. [music] I'm a fan of
their stuff. I'm a fan of how quickly
they innovate.
This was their 360 camera 2 years ago.
This was last year. And this is their
latest flagship 360 camera. [music] I
think the the best way to sum up what
what this is what the innovation here is
I feel like this was like consumer
maybe. This was more prosumer. And this
latest offering, it it verges on like a
professional capable 360 camera.
>> [music]
>> Behind me here is the Park Avenue Tunnel
on 33rd Street. Now, technically,
legally, you're never allowed to like go
through it. Technically, but they opened
it today for everyone. It's all bikes
going through the tunnel.
>> [music]
>> Are we allowed to go on this?
>> I
I mean, there's no no tape.
>> All right, we found a staircase in the
tunnel.
I mean, no one's here. There's no signs
that say you can't go up here.
But, check this out.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Now, you can film me now.
>> Casey!
>> Hi.
>> [music]
>> What do you think this is?
>> It's got to be that. Excellent.
>> Do you think this opens?
>> Yeah. Do you want to pull?
Maybe.
>> No, there's that It's definitely a
That's either a ground or an alarm. So,
I'm just going to leave. We should get
out of here.
>> All right.
All right, let's go.
>> [music]
>> Hey, Casey!
>> Happy Summer Streets!
>> [music]
[music]
>> Come on, bro.
>> So, so this has dual 1-in sensors in it.
That means you get, you know, better
dynamic range, much better low light. It
means when you're shooting 360, you're
shooting at an 8K 50 frames per second.
It also means that when you have one of
the lenses off, you shoot like you would
use this like a like an action camera.
You have that full 1-in sensor behind
it, which makes this a really good
action camera.
It makes me wonder what the future of
action cameras is if this is just going
to kind of cannibalize everything in
that genre.
>> [music]
>> Okay, this is equally elusive on foot or
skateboard or bike, but the little route
around Grand Central is open.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> Have a good day.
You see these ladies?
>> [music]
>> Sometimes you'll see rock bands playing
in this city, but I've never seen a band
before that's all like
middle-aged women just rocking out.
>> [music]
[music]
>> These ladies These ladies are awesome.
>> They're so good.
>> They're shredding.
>> I just want to say hi. I'm such a
big fan.
>> How's your Summer Streets going?
>> The best, right?
>> [music]
>> How's your Summer Streets going?
>> Great, great. We do it every year.
>> you What's your mobility uh
>> You're looking at it. You
>> No, I'm
>> It's not electric.
>> I'm more of a skateboard guy myself. You
guys look great on those scooters.
>> Thank you.
>> When you do a brand deal [music] for
like Insta360, they send you this
internal confidential
um spec list. It's all the
specifications of this device and they
want you to talk about those specs.
Things like um dual custom Sony 1 1.1 in
sensors, industry first native Dolby
Vision plus 10-bit color, in-house
developed 360 AI multi-modal model zero
editing for It's hard for me to get
excited about specs. I'm I don't care
about specs. I'm not a huge gear guy.
For me,
something either works or it doesn't. It
does the job I want it to do or it's
something that stands in my way. A good
example is this camera I'm talking to
you now on, this big SLR camera right
here. See it?
I got this camera like eight or nine
years ago and since getting it, there's
never a need for me to upgrade. It just
does what I want. It's like a hammer. It
always works. I never thought of a 360
camera like that. It's always am I doing
something actiony, do I want a weird
shot? That's where 360 camera fits in.
But because because of how like dynamic
the capabilities are of this, it's now
something that I'll always bring with
me.
>> [music]
>> I'm going on a fun little adventure with
Jordan to look at Summer Streets. Bring
this.
Yo, Jordan. I know it's going to work in
low light. I know it's going to I just
throw it out there, click record and the
shot's going to look good. I also know I
can cut it in with this footage.
>> [music and singing]
[music and singing]
>> This moment in particular, like this guy
had a DJ set up, a little one, a laptop
on his lap while he was riding his city
bike. And I was holding my SLR trying to
film him, but I wanted a shot right in
front of his bike. I threw Jordan this
SLR camera. He threw me this on a selfie
stick and I was riding next to him with
the camera right
>> [singing and music]
>> That's how I got that shot.
>> [music]
>> And I knew
that it would cut in well enough with
this huge fancy pro camera. It would
look good enough where I wouldn't have
to worry about it.
>> Water bottle tripod not recommended.
>> For this, I thought it'd be funny if
like Jordan and I had a back and forth
while we were eating.
It ended up not being that great. The
dialogue was wasn't good, but
I decided to shoot it on this instead of
this because I could do that switch
panning thing.
>> They should do it year-round. They
should do it every weekend.
>> Why don't you not Why don't you eat your
food first, Jordan?
>> Thank you very [music] much, sir.
Good job.
>> Thank you.
I think the takeaway here is that with
all the technical innovation in this
camera, it's no longer just for like
crazy 360 shots or for action shots.
It's now just a camera I always have to
have with me cuz I know it's always
going to get the shot cuz it can always
do the thing, whatever that thing is.
Nice work, Insta360. Thanks for
sponsoring the video.
Now, I got to get back to the wife and
kids.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I'm home.
>> [music]